{
    "items": [
        {
            "question": "Which Protocol do Internet Browsers (Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer) use?",
            "options": [
                "SMTP",
                "FTP",
                "AOL",
                "HTTPS"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Layer 6 of OSI model?",
            "options": [
                "Physical",
                "Presentation",
                "Network",
                "Transport"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Within the Session Layer, what connection allows applications to talk through ports?",
            "options": [
                "Ports",
                "Ethernet",
                "Sockets",
                "IPP"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "When a sender wants to know the physical address of a device it broadcasts what?",
            "options": [
                "ARP Request",
                "Checksum",
                "Broadcast Request",
                "ARP Reply"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What is an Internet Control Message Protocol to check if a destistination device is responding?",
            "options": [
                "UDP Reply",
                "ICMP Test",
                "ICMP Reply",
                "ICMP Ping"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "In 2020 nearly all websites use what type of cryptographic protocol?",
            "options": [
                "Transport Layer Security",
                "Secure Socket Layer",
                "Transfer Layer Security",
                "Secure Layer Security,"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "What OSI layer does Chrome and other browsers use TLS to encrypt data?",
            "options": [
                "Application",
                "Network",
                "Session",
                "Presentation"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which network protocol is often used for video game streaming in which some packet drop is preferable to overall latency?",
            "options": [
                "Connectionless Protocol",
                "User Datagram Protocol",
                "Transmission Control Protocol",
                "File Transfer Protocol"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Which network protocol type can establish a secure connection before sending data?",
            "options": [
                "Connectionless Protocol",
                "User Datagram Protocol",
                "Transmission Control Protocol",
                "File Transfer Protocol"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of small pieces of information sent via TCP/IP?",
            "options": [
                "Packets",
                "Capsules",
                "Data points",
                "Files"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        }
    ]
}
